[{"answer": "Well, you don't want me to tell you on this show.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 4, "question": "What's rude sex?", "qSentId": 3}, {"answer": "Yes, you go hair spray, a little something.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "But really?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "I don't make a lot of them.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Michele Bachmann, Sarah Palin -- what do you make of it?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "But you know what's so interesting about our politics in this country is you are what you looked like.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Whereas you have the Tea Party who are gathering the momentum, have a huge following behind them, where there's Rick Perry or Michele Bachmann or whatever, but there is still a sense of what would we be getting ourselves into if they actually governed the country?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "I'm not happy with it.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "What do you think of Barack Obama's performance?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "I live here, oh, over 20 years.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "How long have you lived in America?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "I do love it.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "You love it, don't you?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "I love London.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "But you're very much an L.A. girl, right?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "And all of the big stars tend to live here, right?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Yes, Marlon Brando was fantastic.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Marlon Brandon?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Give me a little taste of it?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Did you grasp why a man would behave like that?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "You're on Twitter all the time.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Who knows?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "Can you imagine doing something like that?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "I personally wouldn't have communication with people I didn't know.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Can you imagine standing in front of a mirror and photographing yourself?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "I think it matters.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Does it matter?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "No, I'm not quietly encouraging it.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Are you not quietly encouraging this kind of behavior?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "They do.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "I want one of those affairs Jackie Collins is writing about?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "Well, you don't want me to tell you on this show.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "What's rude sex?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "ORGAN: So, I know you weren't born four years before me.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Where are you going with this?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "I'm a one man band.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "How do you preserve yourself so brilliantly?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "She's in the sun all the time, Piers.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Joan's big secret is she never goes to the sun, hasn't done since she's 21, right?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Not recently, but the last time I was there, she was there.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "You were in Saint-Tropez?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "When I came to America, being English, I threw myself out on my pool every day.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Were you like that?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "I think it's because I write characters that they are interested in.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "What is the secret of continuing to write books that people buy in such huge numbers, do you think?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Well, there's no best way to deal with it.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "What do you think having been through this now several times, what do you recommend to people?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "I live my life like an affluent bachelor.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Are you still on the dating scene?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "It means when I was a kid growing up, I would read my father's \"Playboy.\"", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "What does it mean?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "I have a man for every occasion.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Oh, well, that would be revealing too much.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "How many occasions are we talking about here?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "I think men are fantastic.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "What's been your overview of the male species?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Should women ever fully trust the man they're with?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "Honest is what I'm afraid you're looking for.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "You're nice on this show, horrendous on the other show -- road to everybody, right?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "I love that.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "How many copies do you think shift to this world?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "JackieJCollins.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "What is your Twitter address?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "It's at @PiersMorgan.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "What is yours?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "I write good sex, that's why.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "What do you think about that?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "I'm very well.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Gloria, how are you?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Titanium reinforced.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "So, I suppose the obvious question for me is how's the back?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "STEFAN: Well, that's where you see I'm going by, because I feel better than ever.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "And when they hit those, sort of, landmarks, that's scary, isn't it?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "No, actually, since 2004 --", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Tell me about this new album because this is the first English speaking album in five years?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "It's a big fun.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "So, what was he like to work with -- same kind of thing?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "I was two year -- just under two years old when you came.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "How old were you at the time?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "I have memories of my father, his smell, the night he left, the day he came back from the Bay of Pigs.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "You have no memory presumably of this?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "None, actually because when he came back from Vietnam, I was about 13 years old and he went downhill very fast.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "How much of your huge success did he get to see?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "STEFAN: I know what he would have made of it because a few years ago, I never listened to those tapes because it breaks my heart.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "What do you think he would -- given that he obviously knew you were musical and anything else, what would he have made of what happen to you?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "No, I can't.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Have you listened to any of them since?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Wepa means absolutely nothing.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "What does it mean?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "Did you scream Wepa when President Obama became president?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "It was transcendent.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "What did you feel in that moment?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "You told the world, you played in almost every country, in some stage, when you see what used to be called emerging countries, China, India, Brazil, and others, really becoming now very faster super powers in their own right, when you see that, are you excited for that potential or like many Americans -- do you feel slightly intimidated and threatened by that?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "No, exactly.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "There's no point having a publicist anymore, isn't it?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "OK, I will let you know.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "Why Emilio?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "You were far away.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Why didn't the rest of us get a shot at it?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Only boyfriend you've ever had?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "There were no male admirers.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "How did you stay still chaste?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "Well, you know, our priority has always been our family.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "How did priorities change after that?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "Actually, I walked again in the hospital after they reconnected me -- but not by myself.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "When was the moment you walked again?", "qSentId": 720}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "That's true love, right?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "Well, go back -- I don't think I could ever live in Cuba because my home is Miami.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 731, "question": "Do you dream wistfully of the day that Castro is gone and you can go back to Cuba?", "qSentId": 730}, {"answer": "Well, I tell you this, my dream both on a personal level and on a professional level -- professional level, to sing in a free Cuba, to share my music with my people.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "Wouldn't you, for the sake of your father, wouldn't it be quite a moment for you to fly to Cuba post-Castro to complete really the job that he start?", "qSentId": 734}, {"answer": "Well, tanning, I -- is a term I dubbed that represents the process of the next generation of kids that no longer see color when they see each other.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 757, "question": "What does this all mean, \"The Tanning of America\"?", "qSentId": 756}, {"answer": "Well, I think social networking did a lot to help intensify the phenomenon.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 761, "question": "How much of that is done through social networking?", "qSentId": 760}, {"answer": "I honestly think that he should speak to what he did with capturing Osama bin Laden.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 770, "question": "-- what would you do?", "qSentId": 769}, {"answer": "Let's talk brands here.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 782, "question": "And, you know, I feel for the fact that he has these headwinds in front of him and you know the Republicans are doing a very good job of painting that picture, like what did he do?", "qSentId": 781}, {"answer": "I think Beyonce.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 785, "question": "Which individuals out there right now do you think has a complete mastery of their brand and at the top of their game?", "qSentId": 784}, {"answer": "You cannot lie to the media.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 814, "question": "Why did his brand collapse?", "qSentId": 813}, {"answer": "Jay-Z.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 826, "question": "Who are the smartest people you've worked with in terms of that?", "qSentId": 825}, {"answer": "I think we need to -- we don't have the -- our export, our cultural -- our biggest export was our culture, you know, our movies, our stars.", "docId": "111015pmt", "aSentId": 841, "question": "But assuming he reads the book and he puts you in charge of rebranding him, remarketing \"America, PLC,\" \"America, Incorporated\" -- what would you do to get this country back on its feet?", "qSentId": 840}]